Some calls are best left unanswered.
The Caller is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Matthew Parkhill.
Troubled divorcee Mary Kee is tormented by a series of
sinister phone calls from a mysterious woman.
When the stranger reveals she's calling from the
past, Mary tries to break off contact.
But the caller doesn't like being ignored, and looks for
revenge in a unique and terrifying way...
Mary Kee, played by Rachelle Lefevre.
John Guidi, played by Stephen Moyer.
George, played by Luis Guzmán.
Steven, played by Ed Quinn.
Rose Lazar, played by Lorna Raver.
Old Woman, played by Lydia Echevarría.
The Caller is a 2011 British supernatural horror film directed by Matthew Parkhill and
written by Sergio Casci, starring Rachelle Lefevre, Stephen Moyer and Lorna Raver.
The movie was filmed entirely in Puerto Rico.
The Gala Premiere of the movie was on August 23,
2011 at Metro Cinema in Puerto Rico.
The film explores themes of female stalker, anonymous telephone call, divorcee.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.